Hi, I'm Richie Pandey.
嗨 我是 Richie Pandey
I'm Richer Cahal.
我是 Richer Cahal
I'm Vienna Harvey.
我是 Vienna Harvey
I'm Brian Okaykay and I'm a Curriculum Manager and self-taught full-stack developer.
我是 Brian Okaykay 我是一名课程经理 并且自学的全栈工程师
I'm manager at self-driving car here at Udacity.
我是优达学城无人驾驶的课程经理
I'm a content creator and software engineer.
我是一名内容制作者和软件工程师
Here at Udacity, I've been developing programs in data science.
在优达学诚 我一直在制作数据科学课程
Let's discuss strategies for learning new technical skills.
让我们来了解一些学习新技能的技巧
Learning a new skill can be really exciting but can also be
学习新技能有时候令人很兴奋 但是
challenging especially in a self-paced online program.
有时候也很有挑战性 尤其是通过在线课程自学
We start by defining a learning path so that we know
我们从制定学习路径开始
what our goals are and that we're making progress towards them.
这样能够明确我们的目标 然后不断向它靠近
A goal can mean to finish a particular course,
目标可以是完成一个特定的课程
or complete a nano degree program and get a new job.
也可以是完成一个纳米学位项目并找到一份工作
Maybe you're just personally curious about
又或者你只是个人单纯地对某个话题感兴趣
a topic and want to broaden your knowledge base.
想拓展你的知识视野
Whatever your goal is,
不管你的目标是什么
try to keep it in mind.
努力把它放在心上
It shapes how you learn.
它会影响你的学习方式
When it comes to goals,
对于目标来说
one strategy is to set short term goals and long-term goals.
一个小技巧是定义一些短期目标和长期目标
If your goal is to complete a project or apply to a certain kind of job,
如果你的目标是完成一个项目或申请某些工作
then you should write an incremental plan to get there.
那么你应该写下一个阶段性的计划来完成它
Knowing specific steps to take or milestones to
明确具体的步骤和里程碑可以帮助你
reach can help you stay on track and not feel overwhelmed.
跟上节奏 不会感到过于困难
Take each step as you achieve it so you
一步一步地完成它们
can see yourself moving closer to your long-term goals.
能够使你距离长期目标越来越近
Keeping yourself accountable to a goal is really important.
对你的目标负责是很重要的
Serious, so important.
真的 非常重要
Set calendar reminders for yourself to keep yourself
设置一些日历提醒 确保自己
accountable and learn some small thing every day.
每天都能学习一些知识
Try to add an additional layer of
试着告诉你的小伙伴和朋友
accountability by telling a partner or a friend about it,
让你为自己要做的事感到更多责任感
or even your coworker, or boss.
你甚至也可以告诉你的同事或老板
Someone you can check on your progress.
一些可以帮助你检查进度的人
Enroll in a program with a buddy to help you stay committed to completing the program.
和小伙伴一起加入项目来帮助你坚定完成项目的决心
Studies show it takes time to form a new habit.
一些研究表明你需要一些时间来养成习惯
So get into the habit of working on your program.
所以试着把完成项目培养成习惯
Once learning becomes a habit,
当它成为习惯之后
it won't take so much effort to sit down and work on you program.
耐心完成课程对你来说就是理所当然了
When you feel like procrastinating,
当你想要开始拖延时
remind yourself why you enrolled in the program in the first place.
提醒自己想一想当初为什么要加入这个课程
To help motivate you.
来帮助鼓励自己
Then, reward yourself when you stick with the habit
然后 在你坚持学习的时候奖励自己
I like to get myself an ice cream cone.
我喜欢奖励自己一块冰淇淋甜筒
Having a plan and checking off smaller items makes
通过制定计划和逐步完成一个个小项目
the larger task of learning a whole new skill seem a bit more approachable.
学习新技能这个重大目标变成了一个可完成的任务
You can even set a goal of finishing one exercise or part of the lesson in one sitting.
你甚至也可以选择完成一个小练习和一部分课程内容当做一个目标
The Udacity classroom has projects and
你也可以使用优达学城教室中的项目
suggested project deadlines that you can use as well.
和推荐的项目截止日期
While these projects are good milestones,
这些项目是很好的里程碑
more importantly they provide
更重要的是
hands-on learning to actively practice the skills that you've got.
它们提供了实战机会来锻炼你学习到的技能
Now, these projects are meant to be challenging.
这些项目会有一些挑战性
I know it can be frustrating to get stuck in
我知道当你被困难的项目卡住时
the middle of a project that is really difficult.
你可能会感到一些沮丧
Ooh.
Ooh.
Oh God.
Oh God.
But those times are often the ones where there's
但正是在这种情况下
more room for exploration and innovation.
你通常有更多可探索和创造的空间
For example, when writing a new function,
比如 当你在写一个新函数时
explain the function in simple sentences or pseudo-code,
你可以先用简单的语言或者伪代码解释一遍
and only then move on to writing the syntax.
然后再继续写语法
Build on things incrementally.
逐步去完成事情
Everyone struggles with it when they learn something new.
每个人在学习新知识时都会有一个挣扎的阶段
Be patient with yourself.
对自己耐心一些
For example, software programmers in the industry have
比如 行业内的软件工程师通常也需要很多年
in several years to become masters in their domain.
才能成为他所在领域的专家
To remind yourself of your goal,
提醒自己你的目标
remember every step is getting you closer to it.
记住每一步都是在向它靠近
Now, when working with code,
现在 当你在编程中遇见困难时
there are a lot of great resources for when you hit a roadblock.
有很多的优秀的资源可以使用
Making mistakes in your code is actually a great way to learn.
在编程中犯错实际上是一个很好的学习机会
A lot of my on code projects are developed one error at a time.
我自己的项目在部署时候也经常会出现错误
One habit and skill good programmers have is to read
优秀程序员的习惯之一是阅读错误信息
error messages and practice figuring out what exactly is not working in the code.
并试着弄清楚具体是哪个部分的代码没有正常运行
Being able to use resources to fix
使用资源修复代码问题
your code is a problem solving skills in and of itself.
本身就是一个解决问题的技能
Community-led sites like Stack Overflow or Udacity's own tool called Knowledge,
社区网站如 Stack Overflow 或者优达学城自己的论坛 Knowledge
where people answer each other's questions can be very useful.
大家会在上面回答彼此提出的问题 会对你非常有用
One of the best ways is just to
另外一个好的办法是
type in an error message into Google and see what comes up.
用谷歌搜索你的错误信息 然后查看找到的结果
Because someone else has probably had the same error and maybe figured out a solution.
因为其他人很可能已经遇见过同样的问题 并且已经找到了解决办法
Also read blog posts and source code to
通过阅读一些博客文章和源代码
see how someone else is thinking through a similar problem.
来查看其他人是如何思考一个类似问题的
Technical concepts can be hard to learn and
一些技术概念可能很难理解
it's normal to get an imperfect solution after the first trial.
在刚开始时找不到完美解决办法是很正常的事
It's highly recommended to start with something that is small,
强烈建议先从一个简单的、能掌握的技能开始
that works and incrementally improve it.
然后去逐步完善提高它
Okay. Let's summarize.
好了 让我们总结一遍
Set goals for yourself and hold yourself
制定一些目标和日历清单
accountable with a schedule or an accountability buddy.
对它们负责或者找一些负责任的小伙伴
Breakdown projects into small goals.
把项目拆分成一个个小目标
Work on incremental parts of the lesson.
阶段性地完成课程
Work, do exercises to make the learning stick.
不断学习和练习来保持进步节奏
Start with pseudo-code and use practice and online resources.
学习从伪代码开始 不断实践和使用在线资源
You've got this. So good luck.
你可以的 祝你好运
Happy learning.
学习愉快